<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim D&#39;Annecy</title>
    <description>Tim&#39;s personal site</description>
    <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/sitemap.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 13:30:26 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 13:30:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>KanbanFlow basics</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;KanbanFlow is a personal task management website that takes your 
Kanban board to the next level! I’ve been using it for a few months 
and I absolutely love it. It has some cool features that can really 
improve your workflow and combines task management with time 
management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sign up and get started, visit 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://kanbanflow.com/&quot;&gt;https://kanbanflow.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-homepage.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the KanbanFlow 
homepage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;creating-and-customizing-a-board&quot;&gt;Creating and customizing a board&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First things first. Let’s create a new board and start putting 
tasks on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;At the top of the page, click the &lt;strong&gt;Select board&lt;/strong&gt; box and click 
&lt;strong&gt;Create board&lt;/strong&gt;. From this page, type in a name for your board and 
click &lt;strong&gt;Next&lt;/strong&gt;. You can change this later, so don’t stress about 
it!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now, set your columns. Starting from the top, these columns will 
set your left-to-right workflow on your Kanban. You might want to 
add a “Holding” or “Waiting” column, but it really depends on your 
workflow. If you’re not sure about what to use, check out the book 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Personal-Kanban-Mapping-Work-Navigating/dp/1453802266/&quot;&gt;Personal Kanban: Mapping work, navigating life by Jim 
Benson&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Click the &lt;strong&gt;Create board&lt;/strong&gt; button when you’re finished.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-create-board.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the KanbanFlow board creation settings 
page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the main Kanban workspace. Each column will hold your tasks 
and you’ll be moving them from left to right as you work. One of 
the coolest features of KanbanFlow is the ability to track the time 
it takes for each task. At the end of a week, it can give you a 
report that helps you understand how much time you spent on each 
task. I use the Pomodoro method (25 minutes working, 5 minute 
break) to organize my time and I also use the stopwatch to track 
longer projects and meetings. If you want to learn more about 
Pomodoros, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://pomodorotechnique.com/&quot;&gt;the Pomoro Techique 
website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The magic starts when you create your first task.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Click the &lt;strong&gt;plus symbol&lt;/strong&gt; at the top of any column. &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-To-do-entry.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot 
of the KanbanFlow To-do entry popup 
window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;From here, you can add a name and a description. We’ll talk 
about Labels, Color, and Responsibility later.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;There are two time boxes at the bottom of the &lt;strong&gt;Add task&lt;/strong&gt; 
window. Enter the amount of time you think it will take you in the 
&lt;strong&gt;Time estimate&lt;/strong&gt; box on the right. Leave the left box unchanged. 
It will update itself when you use the timer. &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-To-do-time-entry.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the 
KanbanFlow To-do entry popup window and focusing on the Time 
Estimate box&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Dates&lt;/strong&gt; tab at the top of the window allows you to add due 
dates that correspond with columns. For example, if a project is 
due next week, I would want to mark that down on my Kanban as in 
the target column “Done.” I would also want to begin working on it 
at a certain point, so I’ll make a due date for “In progress.” 
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-To-do-dates.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the KanbanFlow To-do entry popup window with the 
Dates tab selected&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Larger tasks can be broken into smaller ones in the &lt;strong&gt;Subtasks&lt;/strong&gt; 
tab at the top of the window. &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-To-do-subtasks.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the KanbanFlow To-do 
entry popup window with the Dates tab 
selected&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that you’ve got a task, you can start working! You don’t have 
to track your time, but the Timer at the bottom left of the page 
allows you to get stats on how long you’ve been working on a 
specific task. It’s a really cool feature that you can use to 
troubleshoot which tasks are taking too much of your time each 
week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-timer.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the KanbanFlow timer popup 
window&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choose a task by clicking on the &lt;strong&gt;Select&lt;/strong&gt; button. When I’m ready, 
I just click “Start,” begin working, and the timer counts down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you finish with a task, just click and drag the task over into 
another column.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-task-drag.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of the KanbanFlow column 
workflow&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When things get rockin and you get used to the website, you can 
really increase your productivity. I love KanbanFlow because it 
allows me to get a zoomed-out overview of all the tasks I have to 
do in the future while allowing me to break down bigger tasks into 
small subtasks. I can brainstorm ideas by adding comments and I can 
keep meeting notes and other snippets of information organized 
directly into the task, making it much easier than having scraps of 
paper everywhere on my desk or having to keep OneNote files in 
order. I can set reminders for myself of upcoming tasks, I can add 
intermediary deadlines to projects to make sure I start working by 
a certain date and time, and I can be reminded of these deadlines 
if I happen to miss them.  I can add tags and colors to every task 
so that I can better sort by priority, task type, project, or any 
other indicator that I set up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;KanbanFlow gives me a great summary of all of the work I’ve 
completed in the Reports and Statistics view and breaks down how 
long it took to complete each task. If I used Pomodoros, I can also 
track which interruptions broke my workflow. If I have to write a 
15-5, track time for a project, or send a progress report email, it 
just takes a few clicks to filter out in progress tasks and only 
display completed items within a specific date range. From this, I 
can see if there are specific tasks that are taking too much of my 
time or if I’ve been interrupted too often by distractions. 
KanbanFlow also has the ability to work in teams. You can break up 
big projects into smaller pieces which you can then assign to 
others. You can make comments and respond to feedback from your 
team. You can add meeting notes and the best part, in my opinion, 
is that you keep all of that information tied to the specific task, 
avoiding the need to keep dozens of single-line emails.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these features come standard in KanbanFlow and I depend on 
it every day to keep me organized and on track with what’s coming 
up on my calendar. I’ve gotten to the point where I wouldn’t work 
without it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s what mine looks like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-07-19-KanbanFlow-mine.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of my KanbanFlow 
board&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/07/19/KanbanFlow-basics.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/07/19/KanbanFlow-basics.html</guid>
        
        <category>tech,</category>
        
        <category>productivity</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Displaying ZawGyi and Myanmar unicode fonts on Chrome</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Chrome doesn’t display Burmese language characters correctly and 
you won’t be able to read anything on websites written in them. 
Both ZawGyi or unicode characters show up as blank boxes and 
there’s no way to change the Language or Input settings in Chrome 
to get them to show up. It’s been this way for 51 versions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-06-24-burmese-font-incorrect.png&quot; alt=&quot;Table of incorrectly rendered Burmese 
font&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/myanmar-font-tools/ckhifbinlmakgeidlbbmplikmcofaedf&quot;&gt;Myanmar Font Tools 
extension&lt;/a&gt; 
on the Chrome Web Store adds the ability to display these 
characters. You can also check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/kominko/mmft&quot;&gt;Github 
repository&lt;/a&gt; if you want to compile 
it yourself. There’s no configuring or tweaking needed and after 
you’ve installed it, pages with Burmese characters will display 
correctly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-06-24-burmese-font-correct.png&quot; alt=&quot;Table of correctly rendered Burmese 
font&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I don’t know why this functionality isn’t available by 
default in Chrome. It’s a slight annoyance, but it should be 
included in the list of languages.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/06/24/viewing-ZawGyi-and-Myanmar-unicode-fonts-on-Chrome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/06/24/viewing-ZawGyi-and-Myanmar-unicode-fonts-on-Chrome.html</guid>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Found! Blurb about renewable energy in a feminist perspective</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I came across a blurb in &lt;a href=&quot;http://flnowarchive.org/wiki/Box_24_Folder_3_Document_30&quot;&gt;a newsletter from Tallahassee 
NOW&lt;/a&gt; 
published in February 1980 that compares nonrenewable energy to 
patriarchy. It’s an interesting perspective and I don’t know much 
about feminist perspectives on renewable energy. I’d love to know 
more about this and learn what types of energy types were suppored 
in the feminist environmental movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-06-24-found-feminist-energy.png&quot; alt=&quot;Snapshot of a newsletter blurb talking about renewable energy in 
a feminist 
perspective&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“ENERGY” – A Women’s Issue&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Loretta Bussiere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Women’s Movement has taught me that “we don’t want a piece of 
the pie” … “cause the pie sucks.” Our nation’s entire male 
intra-structure is based totally and completely on “oil”–a 
resource soon to run out and possible cause the third male “cock” 
war. Alternative Technology, also known as Appropriate Technology 
is a feminist technology. What do men say about solar, and about 
wind? They call them passive … they are renewable. This is the 
opposite of what is male dominated. It is job producing, it is 
not inflationary and best of all, it’s not controlled by men. 
This means that women can enter these markets without threatening 
men–this can be a future, an economic base of our country that 
we can play a role in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;NOW needs to start following the politics of energy–both on the 
Federal level and in every state. When Governor Graham released 
his Energy Legislative package last week, Talahassee NOW or even 
state NOW should have taken a long hard look at it–a woman’s 
look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Women are in an obvious position to say, not, “we want a piece of 
the pie,” but, “we’re going to redefine the pie.” We are in the 
movement for economic democracy and when we win it, and we will 
because we have to, it’s going to be better for everybody–not 
just women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/06/24/found-feminist-energy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/06/24/found-feminist-energy.html</guid>
        
        <category>art,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Found! Feminist drawings of women</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here’s a collection of interesting drawings that I’ve come across 
in newsletter archives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sexuality-and-family-planning-perspectives-for-the-mentally-ill-and-handicapped&quot;&gt;Sexuality and family planning: Perspectives for the mentally ill and handicapped&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-sexuality-and-family-planning.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a mentally ill woman&quot; title=&quot;Sexuality and family planning: Perspectives for the mentally ill and handicapped&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EntreNous No. 13, March 1989, p. 18&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sketch-of-a-woman-by-aaron-sopher&quot;&gt;Sketch of a woman by Aaron Sopher&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-sketch-of-a-woman.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a woman crying&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Focus on Health review published in 1971 by the Westinghouse Learning Corporation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;abortions-and-the-poor&quot;&gt;Abortions and the poor&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-abortions-and-the-poor.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a woman holding a child.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alan Guttmacher Institute advertisement for their publication Abortions and the Poor: Private Morality, Public Responsibility from 1977.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;drawings-of-a-crying-pregnant-woman&quot;&gt;Drawings of a crying pregnant woman&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-abortion-ten-years-on-one.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a crying pregnant woman cleaning&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-abortion-ten-years-on-two.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a crying pregnant woman with many children in bed&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-abortion-ten-years-on-three.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a crying pregnant woman studying&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Abortion: Ten Years On,” published in 1978 by the Birth Control Trust in London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;take-care-of-your-ovaries-kid&quot;&gt;Take care of your ovaries, kid!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-04-22-comic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Well, can&#39;t stop to talk now -- gotta get to my C.R. group -- then there&#39;s a N.O.W. meeting after that. Take care of your ovaries, kid!&quot; title=&quot;Well, can&#39;t stop to talk now -- gotta get to my C.R. group -- then there&#39;s a N.O.W. meeting after that. Take care of your ovaries, kid!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University of Florida Radical Women in Gainesville Historical Exhibit. WomaNews, Volume 2, Number 9. Published October 1976.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;pensacola-now-meeting&quot;&gt;Pensacola NOW meeting&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-pensacola-now-meeting.png&quot; alt=&quot;Sketch of a Pensacola National Organization for Women (NOW) meeting.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pensacola NOW newsletter, Volume 3, Number 8. Published November 1975.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;manatee-now-against-rape&quot;&gt;Manatee NOW against Rape&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016-05-31-manatee-now-against-rape.png&quot; alt=&quot;Drawing of a woman.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manatee NOW newsletter, Volume 3, Number 2. Published February 1976.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/05/31/found-feminist-drawings.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/05/31/found-feminist-drawings.html</guid>
        
        <category>art</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introduction to  &quot;Observations on mental health in the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe&quot; by Henry P. David (1968)</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Today, more than 50 years after the October 1917 revolution, 
Soviet life reflects a mixture of ageless Russian culture, 
evolving Marxist ideology and the dynamics of modern technology. 
The most significant aspect of Soviet life is that it is planned, 
with central direction residing in the state. There is 
considerable pressure toward conformity, toward behaving in a 
socially and politically acceptable fashion. There is a relative 
de-emphasis of personal needs in favor of the primacy of the 
collective to which the individual is expected to yield.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;From birth through nursery school and all the school grades and 
Communist Party youth organizations, the Soviet child is reared 
to function as a member of the collective. Personality 
development and behavior change are achieved through group 
rewards and punishments. Individual achievements are considered 
in terms of their value to the collective. Membership in a 
collective provides identification, a sense of personal 
well-being, and satisfaction of material and emotional needs. It 
serves to socialize the Soviet child and to strengthen early 
acceptance of the values of adult society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The concept of the collective also dominates university life. 
Both undergraduate and graduate students are fully aware that 
they receive a very expensive state-subsidized education, plus 
cost-of-living stipends. There seems to be an understanding that 
this education is provided because the larger collective–the 
people of the Soviets–need the student’s talents and the 
resulting contribution he is expected to make. This is in concert 
with the Soviet attitude that every citizen, whether male or 
female, should contribute to society which, in turn, will meet 
his need for social security. One Soviet colleague put it this 
way, “I don’t have to save for a rainy day. I know I will always 
have a job or a pension. Medical care is free and our children 
will be educated without any cost to us”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/05/25/introduction-to-observations-on-mental-health.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2016/05/25/introduction-to-observations-on-mental-health.html</guid>
        
        <category>Soviet,</category>
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Women&#39;s Studies Master&#39;s thesis project overview paper</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just submitted my Thesis Project Overview paper to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://ufdc.ufl.edu&quot;&gt;UF 
Digital Collections&lt;/a&gt;. Once it’s accepted, UFDC 
will store my paper so that anyone can read it. Kinda scary to 
think it’s available for everyone to see, but it’s too late to 
change it now! If you’re interested in reading it but you can’t 
access it, I’ve embedded the file in this post. If you have any 
feedback or further questions, please &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#116;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#121;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;send me an 
email&lt;/a&gt; and I’d love to speak with you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://onedrive.live.com/embed?cid=AE0E1D832FB8F14F&amp;amp;resid=AE0E1D832FB8F14F%21311&amp;amp;authkey=ABcY40QLVKgiD-s&amp;amp;em=2&amp;amp;wdStartOn=1&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;600px&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/07/15/wst-thesis.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/07/15/wst-thesis.html</guid>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Florida NOW State Conference bio</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m speaking about my project at this year’s Florida NOW State 
Conference in a few weeks! I’m very excited about this opportunity 
and I can’t wait to receive feedback on the site and the project as 
a whole!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write a short bio and I thought I’d post it here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Tim D’Annecy was raised by a former pastor and graduated from a 
conservative Baptist high school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;During his first semester in college, he was introduced to 
feminism by Helen Strain and began volunteering with Planned 
Parenthood of North Florida. It was through this experience that 
feminism “clicked.” Tim realized he wanted to learn more and 
went on to pursue a Master’s in Women’s Studies. Tim became 
fascinated with the history of feminism when he came across some 
old documents from Gainesville NOW. After finding more 
information about the organization in the university Special 
Collections, Tim created a collaborative website so that 
everyone could be able to access and learn from chapter 
newsletters and notes between activists in North Florida.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This past year, Tim has been working diligently on this archival 
project and he recently presented his website to Gainesville NOW 
and the community in March. In the next few years, he hopes to 
bring his technology skills and feminist perspective and pursue a 
Master’s in Library and Information Science. He can be contacted 
at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#116;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#121;&amp;#064;&amp;#117;&amp;#102;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#100;&amp;#117;&quot;&gt;&amp;#116;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#121;&amp;#064;&amp;#117;&amp;#102;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#101;&amp;#100;&amp;#117;&lt;/a&gt; and the Florida 
NOW website is located at 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://flnowarchive.org/&quot;&gt;http://FLNOWarchive.org/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/04/29/florida-now-state-conference-bio.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/04/29/florida-now-state-conference-bio.html</guid>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Digital humanities critical pedagogy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wrote this paper for a course, but I’m not too happy with it. I 
might come back later and edit it when I have time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://onedrive.live.com/embed?cid=AE0E1D832FB8F14F&amp;amp;resid=AE0E1D832FB8F14F%21606&amp;amp;authkey=AGIekgv9Oxlova0&amp;amp;em=2&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;600px&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/04/22/digital-humanities-critical-pedagogy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/04/22/digital-humanities-critical-pedagogy.html</guid>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Digital humanities undergraduate course website</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For one of my classes, I had to write an overview of a course 
website for my conceptual undergraduate class, “Introduction to 
Humanities Computing.” I wanted to have a site that fulfills the 
fundamental “ontological commitments” of Digital Humanities: 
openness, collaboration, collegiality and connectedness, diversity, 
and experimentation &lt;a href=&quot;https://paperpile.com/c/4O2eZN/FQSO/?locator=25-30&quot;&gt;(Spiro 
25-30)&lt;/a&gt;. My 
class prioritizes digital publishing and this course site is the 
facilitator for this type of work. I will explain this concept 
further, but, simply put, I wanted this site be primarily a space 
where students could make their writings public and talk about 
their progress. The site I wish to create would have an inviting 
atmosphere for collaboration where all students feel connected to 
each other and their work is valued. Students should be able to get 
feedback on their work and feel comfortable giving feedback or 
suggesting changes, no matter how long the post is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To best explain these concepts for the site, I created a blank 
Wordpress and added a blog post that I wrote for one of my classes 
for an example. I also wrote a few generic comments and questions 
from students and replied to them as if I was the professor. All 
content in the site example is mine except the theme, which was 
created by the Wordpress developers. I’ll discuss a few different 
important parts about the site in the following sections and then 
I’ll conclude by talking about how this type of site could benefit 
the students in the near future. I’ve provided screenshots of the 
site and explained the general concept of what each image 
addresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the class Wordpress, I decided to use the &lt;a href=&quot;http://p2theme.com/&quot;&gt;P2 
theme&lt;/a&gt;. This theme looks different from a 
traditional blog website in that it allows users to interact on the 
site as they would with Facebook. Where a traditional blog layout 
would focus on displaying only one post on each page, this layout 
uses a Facebook Timeline-type layout that displays everything on a 
(lengthy) single page. For me - and I’m sure this is the case 
for other students that grew up with technology - this layout 
is intuitive and it behaves in a way that I’m familiar with. The 
theme prioritizes real time communication and I chose to use this 
layout for my course website because it moves away from traditional 
static posts. In the past, I have been in classes where the site 
layout doesn’t do any favors in getting a conversation started 
online. Students write an essay in Word and copy and paste it to 
the blog, they click “Save,” and never look at it 
again. After that, they don’t care enough about their classmates’ 
work, so there’s no reason for them to stay on the class site. By 
midterms, I find that these sites become a dumping ground for class 
essays. Usually, the professor implements a rule that each student 
must make one post and comment on three different posts to receive 
full points - an approach and an issue that I wanted to 
avoid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The class website should be a place where students can go and think 
out loud about their work. I want to foster a place where students 
don’t feel like they have to post huge essays or How-To guides 
every time they visit. A Tweet or Status Update posted on the site 
can be thought of as a comment made in class and I plan to grade 
students’ participation based partly on their use of the site. The 
following sections will discuss my ideas for an ideal course 
website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-04-18-screenshot1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Site screenshot 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A main part of this undergraduate class requires each student to 
write a 500 word blog post each week about the assigned readings or 
the tools that they used for that week. This is a crucial part of 
the course as it makes sure every student is keeping up to date on 
the weekly topics that we’ve discussed. It is also important for 
the students to pause and reflect on the work they completed during 
the week and to connect with other students about issues or 
concerns they might have. I feel that this reflexivity in research 
is fundamental to the completeness of one’s work and I wish to 
foster that practice on my site. The grading for these blog post 
assignments will be subjective, but I will prioritize completion 
and whether they meet the deadline. I will never deduct points from 
a post if the student was unable to complete the task they wanted 
or if they received a different outcome. For example, if a student 
wants to import a logo into a map or timeline (as shown in the next 
screenshot) and find that the system has a bug, I find this process 
of exploration and “play” can often teach more than blind luck. 
Overall, if students are able to write a post explaining what 
outcome they wanted, the process they used, and the result of their 
work, they will be fulfilling the goals of the course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-04-18-screenshot2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Post content example&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As shown in the screenshot below, students can post quick Status 
Updates on the site that can facilitate conversation or get 
technical help. This tool is almost like Twitter or a Facebook 
status that’s meant to be quick, gut feelings or reactions. They 
don’t necessarily have to be polished work like the Blog Posts and 
they certainly won’t be 500 words long, but these informal notes 
are important to make students feel comfortable speaking their 
mind. When the longer assignments come, the students will build 
upon the positive experiences that they had previously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-04-18-screenshot3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Status Update screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the Status Update is posted, other students in the class can 
answer questions and have a conversation about whatever the topic 
is. They can help answer their classmates’ questions and give 
feedback for projects on subjective issues of design and usability. 
This correspondence is important for group learning and is one of 
the Digital Humanities ontological commitments - two aspects 
I wish to address in this course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-04-18-screenshot4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Conversation thread screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the professor or Teaching Assistant wishes to communicate with 
the class, they have a space where they can give the students a 
public response. For example, in this type of public format, other 
students can read the answers given and can ask other questions for 
clarification. If students want to send a situation-specific 
question, they can always send the instructor a direct email or 
message through the course website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-04-18-screenshot5.png&quot; alt=&quot;Conversation thread screenshot 2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the advantages that this type of site gives is the ability 
to collectively organize the students’ thoughts and to create a 
working, in-depth site for others to use. It would be ideal if the 
site could be a reference for other researchers who are working on 
similar projects with these tools. On every entry, students can tag 
their post so that it can be organized by category. Whether the tag 
is “visibility” or another conceptual issue, or a specific tool, 
visitors to the site can navigate and quickly find what they need. 
For instance, if a student writes about Omeka at the beginning of 
the semester and it gets buried by other posts, you can click on 
the entry for Omeka on the sidebar and quickly find the post. 
(Refer back to the first screenshot of the site.) If another 
student writes a response to an article and how it relates to their 
research, the post could be tagged according to the topic discussed 
or the journal from which it came. The syllabus explains that it is 
important to explain the students’ research process, not simply 
give an overview or summary of a reading, so the student must 
emphasize how that reading is applicable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to keep the site private during the semester so that 
students can feel comfortable asking questions and thinking out 
loud. Whether they post something “stupid” or their ideas are good 
enough to be stolen, I wouldn’t want their posts to be made public 
as they’re hesitantly posting their ideas and processes only to be 
exploited by someone on the internet. When the semester is 
finished, I would ask for permission to make these posts public as 
I feel it can benefit other people working on digital projects. I 
would redact or delete any comment or post, if asked, and I can 
always provide the students an exported version of their posts. As 
everything that students post will be available on the internet 
after making the site public, I would need to make sure that they 
had a basic understanding about copyright and Creative Commons 
licensing that they can employ to protect their intellectual 
property. This discussion about ownership could be started as an 
in-class discussion supplemented with videos and other how-to 
manuals available on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright aside, by making the site public, blog posts can be 
considered a form of digital publishing. As everything in academic 
work seems to be moving online, students can build their CV with 
these blog posts and have a tangible source to point to when 
listing their proficiencies. If a student writes a guide about a 
new tool that they were able to use for their research, a quick 
Google Search could associate Student with Marketable Skill. For 
example, if a student writes a quick guide on how to setup OHMS, a 
tool to work interactively with oral history recordings, a stranger 
could acknowledge their technical prowess about that newly created 
tool. The student’s CV would reflect their proficiency and list 
their oral history project with a link to the class site. These 
connections could spur collaboration, career advancement, and 
goodwill with other researchers and users of new technologies. 
After the semester is completed, the course website can serve as 
more than an arena for communication and collaboration, it can be 
an example of a marketable digital portfolio where students can 
showcase their abilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This desire to make posts public is dual-purpose: (1) I feel it is 
an ethical responsibility as a professor to foster critical 
thinking about future career and academic plans. (2) I also feel it 
is important to demonstrate to students the applicability of the 
work done within the course to the “real world” they will be 
working in after graduation. Although it hasn’t been the typical 
format for most academic classes (particularly in the humanities) 
up to this point, skills-based training is and will be crucial for 
the coming changes in the fields. When learning, students should 
understand the conceptual and the technical aspect of these new 
tools and often these two aspects are interchangeable. In a way, 
these concepts can be thought of as two sides of one coin. One 
could argue that disciplinary methodology is important and students 
should be taught Best Practices as a base and technology will come 
later. Others, particularly in STEM fields, may feel that the 
technology is the crucial lesson that should be taught - the 
rules will be learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see that the best approach to this type of work views both 
technology and methodology as interconnected and interdependent. If 
a student has experience and understands the methodological 
importance of a timeline or mapping tool, technical training could 
be helpful. If one is resistant to put the time into detailed and 
technical metadata, a project in which specificity is required 
could change their perception on the issue (as it did for me). 
Digital Humanities should not follow division of traditional 
disciplinary lines: STEM is technology, Humanities and Social 
Sciences are methods. Courses that teach Humanities Computing 
should be critical of this split and work blend both disciplines 
into a workable and reflexive pedagogy. Although theoretical, my 
course as represented through this site is an extension of this 
type of teaching and can be considered an example of how to best 
introduce these new research practices to students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/04/18/undergraduate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/04/18/undergraduate.html</guid>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Found! &quot;Be nice&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I came across an interesting quote &lt;a href=&quot;http://flnowarchive.org/mediawiki/index.php/Box_28_Folder_10_Document_20&quot;&gt;in a newsletter from 
2000&lt;/a&gt; 
by a member of the University of Florida campus NOW chapter during 
a reelection campaign:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Feminism doesn’t mean “be nice,” I would like more open debate. 
All these appeals to sisterhood-just because you don’t agree with 
somebody doesn’t mean you don’t like the person. It’s a thing 
that we need to work out. “Be nice” - I don’t like that idea. We 
want to be a united front but we also don’t want to crush each 
other with everyone trying to be nice to everybody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/03/26/found-be-nice.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/03/26/found-be-nice.html</guid>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Found! Poem from a Pensacola NOW</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I found an interesting poem from a woman who stepped down from her 
position as chapter president in 1973. Margaret Fifield writes to 
the members of Pensacola NOW &lt;a href=&quot;http://flnowarchive.org/mediawiki/index.php/Box_23_Folder_1_Document_2&quot;&gt;in a 
letter&lt;/a&gt; 
that makes me wonder what else went on in the chapter. What led her 
to write this poem?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are like sheep 
They’ll follow anybody 
Just so they don’t have to lead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are lambs&lt;br /&gt;
Being led to the slaughter&lt;br /&gt;
Innocently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are like mules&lt;br /&gt;
Plodding along through the mire&lt;br /&gt;
Hoping everything will be O.K., tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are like rabbits&lt;br /&gt;
So busy hopping about that they&lt;br /&gt;
Can not (or will not) admit what’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are like parrots&lt;br /&gt;
Talking a lot&lt;br /&gt;
But saying nothing that is new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are like dogs&lt;br /&gt;
With a bone of contention&lt;br /&gt;
Until something more valuable comes along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some feminists are like snakes&lt;br /&gt;
Slithering about very carefully&lt;br /&gt;
Always in control of themselves, and any situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;But the worst feminists of all&lt;br /&gt;
Are like poisonous snakes, destroying anyone around&lt;br /&gt;
Who doesn’t watch where she’s going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Too bad some feminists aren’t more human&lt;br /&gt;
Then they could read the signs&lt;br /&gt;
That say: “Beware of Snakes:”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/03/01/found-pensacola-NOW-poem.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/03/01/found-pensacola-NOW-poem.html</guid>
        
        <category>art,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Project proposal</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wrote this paper as a quick update to my thesis committee. At 
this point, I feel overwhelmed with the amount of work that I have 
to do to and I need to get more organized if I’m going to finish 
strong. Not only do I have to manage my time, I may have to reframe 
the scope of the project to something a bit more reasonable. If I 
had five years, I’m sure I could do the whole collection but I 
won’t finish working through the entire collection in the time I 
have left in this master’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In any case, here’s an update of my work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; src=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/159X37TVOIAG4Hk5ZEhCPGTJeOZJfYVDMOCdgoQI9PQ4/pub?embedded=true&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/02/19/project-proposal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/02/19/project-proposal.html</guid>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Found! Uterus comic</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I came across a funny comic in &lt;a href=&quot;http://flnowarchive.org/mediawiki/index.php/Box_24_Folder_3_Document_30&quot;&gt;one of the 
newsletters&lt;/a&gt; 
from Tallahassee NOW dated February 1980. Thought I’d share it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-01-01-found-uterus-comic.png&quot; alt=&quot;uterus comic&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transcription:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Left: So the doctor says to me, “Why not have your uterus 
removed; You’re not using it, and it’ll save you a lot of trouble 
in the long run.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Right: If a man had a uterus, it would be like a landmark 
building, you’d need a court order to remove it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Reprinted from “I’m in Training to be Tall and Blonde,” by Nicole 
Hollander.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/01/01/found-uterus-comic.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/01/01/found-uterus-comic.html</guid>
        
        <category>art,</category>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Found! Feminist organizational chart</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While working through a folder on the Florida NOW archive, I found 
a sketch of a few organizational charts from several different 
organizations in &lt;a href=&quot;http://flnowarchive.org/mediawiki/index.php/Box_24_Folder_3_Document_14&quot;&gt;one of the 
newsletters&lt;/a&gt; 
dated 1978. I’m not sure if this is satirical or if “Arab” is 
supposed to be a joke, but I think it’s interesting to see how 
these feminist organizers saw the leadership structure of the 
women’s liberation movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015-01-01-found-feminist-organizational-chart.png&quot; alt=&quot;Feminist organizational chart scanned from a newsletter dated 1978&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/01/01/found-organizational-chart.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tdannecy.mehttp://tdannecy.me/2015/01/01/found-organizational-chart.html</guid>
        
        <category>politics,</category>
        
        <category>school</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
